<whacks>

<attackperp>is viciously attacked by you wildly swinging a</attackperp>
<attackperp>gets a sudden vicious attack from you with a</attackperp>
<attackperp>steps in and you savagely attack them swinging a</attackperp>
<attackperp>looks you in the eye as you cut a wide arc swinging a</attackperp>
<attackperp>smells your desperation as you use all your might to attack with a</attackperp>

<attackvic>surprises you with a vicious attack wildly swinging a</attackvic>
<attackvic>suddenly assaults you with a</attackvic>
<attackvic>steps in and attacks you swinging a</attackvic>
<attackvic>attacks flailing at you in a wide arc with a</attackvic>
<attackvic>strikes you with all their might with a</attackvic>

<whack>finds it's mark spraying blood everywhere opening a big gash in</whack>
<whack>digs in and splatters blood across the jungle from a gash in</whack>
<whack>connects splattering blood bright red against the dark green jungle fresh from</whack>
<whack>hacks deeply spewing blood in the face of</whack>
<whack>slams with a sickening wet thud into</whack>

<whacker>reels backwards screaming in pain from your</whacker>
<whacker>screams in agony and grabs at the wound left by your</whacker>
<whacker>falls wounded in a heap from the blast of your</whacker>
<whacker>drops like a wet sack of fertilizer from the mighty blow of your</whacker>
<whacker>grunts and staggers stunned by the blow from your</whacker>

<whacked>dances and hoots as you reel backwards screamning in pain.</whacked>
<whacked>screams a war cry as you grab at your wound.</whacked>
<whacked>waves his weapon in the air as you fall wounded.</whacked>
<whacked>steps back to eye the results as you drop like a wet sack of fertilizer.</whacked>
<whacked>grunts crazily as you stagger from the blow.</whacked>

<miss>is fanned with the near miss of</miss>
<miss>nimbly side steps the wild swinging of</miss>
<miss>ducks and is missed completely by</miss>
<miss>steps aside at the last moment and deflects the strike of</miss>
<miss>with surprising speed blocks the blow from</miss>

<misser>darts side to side looking for an opening.</misser>
<misser>dances to and fro sizing you up.</misser>
<misser>looms menacingly as you decide flight or fight.</misser>
<misser>circles in a threatening manner.</misser>
<misser>sizes you up greedily eyeing your sack.</misser>

<missed>whistles right by your ear without effect!</missed>
<missed>barely misses your skull!</missed>
<missed>only fans you with a wild miss!</missed>
<missed>doesn't even come close to you!</missed>
<missed>whips past as you easily duck and side step!</missed>

<stumble>You stagger from hunger and thirst, too weak to continue much further.</stumble>
<stumble>You stumble and grow weaker, barely able to make a few moves more.</stumble>
<stumble>You fall to your knees and are barely able to get up you're so weak.</stumble>
<stumble>You collapse suddenly growing weaker, momentarily blacking out.</stumble>
<stumble>Your knees buckle and send you sprawling, you stagger to your feet unable to continue much further.</stumble>
<stumble>Your vision blurs as your hunger and thirst sap your strength to the point of collapse.</stumble>

<message>Far off drums bring a message from</message>
<message>Drumbeats on a hollow log bring a message from</message>
<message>Ungowa! Drums speak with message from</message>
<message>You hear distant drum beats of a message from</message>
<message>Nearby drums bring a message from</message>

<snatch>You slip your hand into</snatch>
<snatch>Gently working your hand around in</snatch>
<snatch>Clumsily fumbling around in</snatch>
<snatch>Groping wildly around in</snatch>
<snatch>Fumbling blindly around in</snatch>

<snatchee>You look in you bag to find</snatchee>
<snatchee>Checking your bag you find</snatchee>
<snatchee>Glancing in your bag you discover</snatchee>
<snatchee>Taking inventory of your bag you discover</snatchee>
<snatchee>You reach in your bag to find</snatchee>

<snatcher>crept in and stole your</snatcher>
<snatcher>has ripped off your</snatcher>
<snatcher>has purloined your</snatcher>
<snatcher>snuck in and stole your</snatcher>
<snatcher>snatched your</snatcher>

<snatched>bag you come up clutching their</snatched>
<snatched>sack you find their</snatched>
<snatched>pouch and come up with their</snatched>
<snatched>satchel only to discover their</snatched>
<snatched>sack and grab their</snatched>

</whacks>

